<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<resources>
  <book>
    <title>How to Stay Christian in College</title>
    <image>resources_html_m3d1cd35a.png</image>
	<location>TEEN 248.8 BUD</location>
	<link>http://www.christianbook.com/how-to-stay-christian-in-college/j-budziszewski/9781576835104/pd/835103</link>
    <description>College campuses are overtly hostile to the Christian faith, and many Christian students give in to defeat. But Professor J. Budziszewski will help prepare you and your parents for the challenges you will encounter, and how to successfully overcome them.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>Fish Out of Water</title>
	<image>resources_html_m4e759ff1.png</image>
	<location>TEEN 248.8 NYE</location>
	<link>http://www.christianbook.com/water-surviving-thriving-christian-secular-campus/abby-nye/9780892216215/pd/216212</link>
	<description>Abby prepares new freshman (and even seasoned students!) to be able to survive and thrive in this often hostile setting. Among the topics she covers are 
	  freshman orientation week,
      the treatment of science and faith in the classroom,
      tifficult professors and real life solutions,
      the mean forms of liberal "indoctrination", and
      telpful campus groups and managing peer pressure.
      This book is truly a must read for students entering any college--a valuable handbook for parents, teachers, and students alike.
	</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>A Ready Defense</title>
	<image>resources_html_m494ec4e8.png</image>
	<location>TEEN 239 MCD</location>
	<link>http://www.christianbook.com/a-ready-defense-josh-mcdowell/9780840744197/pd/42816</link>
	<description>Here is evidence for the Christian faith by one of its premier defenders! Topically arranged, this "Best of Josh McDowell" gives you more than 60 well-reasoned arguments from creation to the virgin birth to the resurrection of Jesus and much more. Ideal for skeptics who are curious about Christianity and for Christians who want to learn how to defend their faith. 566 pages, softcover from Nelson.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>Simple Tools For Brain Surgery</title>
	<image>resources_html_748132b7.png</image>
	<location>VID 239 SIM</location>
	<link>http://www.christianbook.com/simple-tools-for-brain-surgery/9780974410494/pd/410498</link>
	<description>When it comes to witnessing, are you intimidated by atheists, new agers, or evolutionists because you don't have all the answers? Bill Jack offers four simple questions that effectively refute secular thinking. "What do you mean by that?" "How do you know?" "So what?" "What if you're wrong?" Try it and you'll discover how easy---and powerful---his approach is!</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>Mind Siege</title>
	<image>resources_html_5db3954b.png</image>
	<location>239 LAH</location>
	<link>http://www.christianbook.com/mind-siege-battle-truth-new-millennium/tim-lahaye/9780849943591/pd/43594</link>
	<description>Tim LaHaye and David Noebel's classic Mind Siege has not lost its relevancy! Each generation must decide if Christ is superior to Nietzsche; if God is exalted above Plato. Your choices will affect the way you live now and where you will spend eternity. LaHaye and Noebel offer a battle plan that arms you with knowledge and practical suggestions to combat worldly wisdom with the Word of God.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>Every Thought Captive</title>
	<image>resources_html_m3e567193.png</image>
	<location>239 PRA</location>
	<link>http://www.christianbook.com/every-thought-captive-richard-pratt/9780875523521/pd/5523528</link>
	<description>In down-to-earth language Richard L. Pratt, Jr., has given us this helpful study manual on apologetics, the task of defending the faith. Far from a theoretical exposition, this training manual teaches how to answer nonbelievers and to "take every thought captive to the obedience of Christ." Pratt shows how the biblical doctrines about humanity and our relationship to our Creator determine how we should do apologetics. Within this theological framework he examines the premises, attitudes, and specific steps involved in a genuinely biblical defense of Christianity. Illustrations and review questions help to make this a valuable tool for individual or group study.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>Lifeviews</title>
	<image>resources_html_1c1bb04f.png</image>
	<location> </location>
	<link>http://www.amazon.com/gp/aw/d/0800753577/ref=redir_mdp_mobile/177-6709252-5985805</link>
	<description>As a Christian, you are called to be a witness of Christ's Gospel, to be "the salt of the earth and the light of the world." How can you make that kind of impact in a society filled with darkness and decay? Dr. R.C. Sproul shows you how in "Lifeviews", a layman's guide to understanding the many non-Christian philosophies and attitudes that affect and influence our contemporary culture. "Lifeviews" offers, though-stimulating, information and insight on confronting today's moral and social issues with an effective biblical response.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>How Now Shall We Live?</title>
	<image>resources_html_m57b2246a.png</image>
	<location>261 COL</location>
	<link>http://www.christianbook.com/how-now-shall-we-live-softcover/charles-colson/9780842355889/pd/55885</link>
	<description>If we are going to respond to Paul's command to "not conform any longer to the teaching of this world, but be transformed by the renewing of your mind" we will need to develop a Christian worldview. In How Now Shall We Live, Colson and Pearcey carefully lay the foundation of a Christian worldview and enable you to develop a Christian perspective on every aspect of life. If you want your faith to help you counter what your children are learning in school, challenge the decadence of popular culture and impact the lives of unsaved family and friends, consider How Now Shall We Live required reading!</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>Unmasking The New Age</title>
	<image>resources_html_1ee5308b.png</image>
	<location>291 GRO</location>
	<link>http://www.christianbook.com/unmasking-the-new-age/douglas-groothuis/9780877845683/pd/5689</link>
	<description>Groothuis shows how the new age movement has influenced our culture---especially in health, psychology and spirituality---and outlines how believers can counter this pervasive, nonchristian worldview. One of the best books on the subject to date.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>Correcting the Cults</title>
	<image>resources_html_27abaaa5.png</image>
	<location> </location>
	<link>http://www.christianbook.com/correcting-expert-responses-their-scripture-twisting/norman-geisler/9780801065507/pd/6550X</link>
	<description>How do cults use scripture to ensnare millions? Discover the ways that Mormonism, Jehovah's Witnesses, the New Age movement, and others misinterpret the Bible to support their own doctrines. Comprehensive, accessible, and intelligent, this reliable resource will equip you to understand aberrant faith systems, reason with their adherents, and point them toward Jesus Christ! Formerly titled When Cultists Ask.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>The Complete Infidel's Guide to the Koran</title>
	<image>resources_html_m46d61f06.png</image>
	<location> </location>
	<link>http://www.christianbook.com/complete-infidels-guide-to-the-koran/robert-spencer/9781596981041/pd/981041</link>
	<description>The Koran: It may be the most controversial book in the world. Some see it as a paean to peace, others call it a violent mandate for worldwide Islamic supremacy. How can one book lead to such dramatically different conclusions? New York Times bestselling author Robert Spencer reveals the truth in The Complete Infidel's Guide to the Koran: not many Westerners know what's in the Koran, since so few have actually read it -- even among the legions of politicians, diplomats, analysts, and editorial writers who vehemently insist that the Koran preaches tolerance. Now, Spencer unveils the mysteries lying behind this powerful book, guiding readers through the controversies surrounding the Koran's origins and its most contentious passages. Stripping out the obsolete debates, Spencer focuses on the Koran's decrees toward Jews, Christians, and other Infidels, explaining how they were viewed in Muhammad's time, what they've supposedly done wrong, and most important, what the Koran has in store for them.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>Reasoning from the Scriptures with Muslims</title>
	<image>resources_html_m54fa10fb.png</image>
	<location>266 RHO</location>
	<link>http://www.christianbook.com/reasoning-from-the-scriptures-with-muslims/ron-rhodes/9780736910101/pd/910107</link>
	<description>Whether you want to share the gospel with Muslims or just better understand the doctrines of Islam, you'll appreciate this thorough reference. Who is Allah? How do the Qur'an and the Bible compare? What are the roles of Jesus and Muhammad? What are the different Islamic groups? The question-and-answer format is a tool you can use!</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>So What's the Difference?</title>
	<image>resources_html_2c9f3065.png</image>
	<location>291.2 RID</location>
	<link>http://www.christianbook.com/difference-faiths-compare-christianity-revised-expanded/fritz-ridenour/9780830718986/pd/718982</link>
	<description>In easy-to-understand chapters, the author explains the basic beliefs of Protestantism, Roman Catholicism, Judaism, Islam, Hinduism, Jehovah's Witnesses, Mormonism, New Age and a dozen other belief systems of the world. It will help you recognize the real differences and make it easier to explain and share your faith with others. Completely revised and updated.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>The Kingdom of the Cults</title>
	<image>resources_html_m5c63750.png</image>
	<location>291.9 MAR</location>
	<link>http://www.christianbook.com/kingdom-the-cults-rev-and-updated/walter-martin/9780764228216/pd/228218</link>
	<description>Radio's original Bible Answer Man Walter Martin's classic resource as updated by cult and occult specialist Ravi Zacharias. Using Martin's well-researched and easily accessible text, Zacharias brings the experience of in-depth study, some would say immersion, into this sometimes confusing field of study and includes many facts and figures covering occurrences in the 1990's (as Martin passed away in 1989). Kingdom of the Cults has always been a trusted resource in times where accurate information is imperative to someone's salvation from the strange world of cults and the occult. Ranging in topics from the structure of cults to how cults are encountered on the mission field, many cults and movements are described in full, and intimate details of the inner workings can sometimes be indicative of where a cult may be leading. For anyone considering joining any of these groups or looking for more information for a friend or family member, this is an invaluable resource.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>Relativism</title>
	<image>resources_html_5fceac8a.png</image>
	<location>239 BEC</location>
	<link>http://www.christianbook.com/relativism-feet-firmly-planted-mid-air/francis-beckwith/9780801058066/pd/58066</link>
	<description>Writing from years of experience in defending Christian values, Beckwith and Koukl offer a critique of moral relativism. They explore the inconsistencies inherent in the relativist position, suggest specific approaches that can be used in the course of dialogue, and consider the everyday implications of relativism, especially in relation to important issues such as: abortion, homosexuality, multiculturalism, political correctness, and tolerance.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>Telling the Truth</title>
	<image>resources_html_m71b23c2a.png</image>
	<location>269.2 CAR</location>
	<link>http://www.christianbook.com/telling-the-truth-evangelizing-postmoderns/9780310243342/pd/43343?</link>
	<description>This thoughtful cultural analysis probes important turning points of biblical theology, describes successful contemporary evangelism, and exposes readers to the strategy and practice of Christian thinkers who are reaching the postmodern world.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>The New Evidence the Demands a Verdict</title>
	<image>resources_html_548d9b9.png</image>
	<location>239 MCD</location>
	<link>http://www.christianbook.com/the-new-evidence-that-demands-verdict/josh-mcdowell/9780785242192/pd/42199</link>
	<description>Christians today face growing challenges to show that their faith is both relevant and credible. In Josh McDowell's The New Evidence That Demands a Verdict, you'll get the ammunition you need to defend your faith against the barrage of criticisms. This 760-page hardcover combines the two original best-selling volumes into one, maintaining their classic defense of the faith, yet answering new questions posed by today's culture.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>Christian Apologetics</title>
	<image>resources_html_m2d14e32.png</image>
	<location>239 GEI</location>
	<link>http://www.christianbook.com/christian-apologetics-norman-geisler/9780801038228/pd/37042</link>
	<description>College and seminary students can be equipped to understand and uphold the validity of the Christian faith. Avoiding the pitfalls of mere emotional arguments, it prepares students intellectually to withstand both the frontal attacks and subtle influences of other worldviews. The book is divided into three parts: surveying, verifying, and applying the unique claims of historical Christianity.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>The Case for Christ</title>
	<image>resources_html_511ac447.png</image>
	<location>232.9 STR</location>
	<link>http://www.christianbook.com/christ-journalists-personal-investigation-evidence-jesus/lee-strobel/9780310209300/pd/20930</link>
	<description>A seasoned journalist chases down the biggest story on record in The Case for Christ. Retracing his own spiritual journey from atheism to faith, former Chicago Tribune legal editor Lee Strobel cross-examines a dozen experts with tough, point-blank questions in search of credible evidence that Jesus of Nazareth was positively the Son of God. This riveting quest for the truth about history's most compelling figure reads like a captivating, fast-paced novel, yet it's anything but fiction! An ideal paperback for skeptics!</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>Defeating Darwinism by Opening Minds</title>
	<image>resources_html_m4435705.png</image>
	<location>576.8 JOH</location>
	<link>http://www.christianbook.com/defeating-darwinism-by-opening-minds/phillip-johnson/9780830813605/pd/13608</link>
	<description>What's the best way to discern and defeat the false claims of Darwinism? By developing solid critical-thinking skills, says Johnson. His non-technical discussion of Darwinism versus creationism gives you sound advice on spotting deceptive arguments, grasping scientific issues, understanding the impact of the Scopes trial, and more. Ideal for high school students, teachers, pastors, or anyone concerned about the creation-evolution debate.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>Icons of Evolution</title>
	<image>resources_html_2ad465d7.png</image>
	<location>576.8 WEL</location>
	<link>http://www.christianbook.com/icons-of-evolution/9780972043311/pd/043311</link>
	<description>Controversy about the theory of evolution has raged since Charles Darwin proposed it in 1859. Through professional and yet engaging interviews with scientific experts you'll come to understand the incorrect assumptions and data used by Darwin—and the scientific facts that refute them.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>Bones of Contention</title>
	<image>resources_html_6a06eeb7.png</image>
	<location>573.3 LUB</location>
	<link>http://www.christianbook.com/contention-creationist-assessment-fossils-revised-updated/marvin-lubenow/9780801065231/pd/65238</link>
	<description>With over 35 years of research in the field of paleoanthropology, Lubenow reveals the philosophical and scientific untruths in the theory of human evolution through the study of hominid fossils. This revised edition of his classic text discusses "scientific racism," clarifies the humanity of Neanderthals and Homo erectus, and references creationist scientists. Includes charts and notes.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>Darwin's Black Box</title>
	<image>resources_html_6c047d1.png</image>
	<location>575 BEH</location>
	<link>http://www.christianbook.com/darwins-biochemical-challenge-evolution-anniversary-edition/michael-behe/9780743290319/pd/290319</link>
	<description>In 1996, Darwin's Black Box helped to launch the intelligent design movement: the argument that nature exhibits evidence of design, beyond Darwinian randomness. It sparked a national debate on evolution, which continues to intensify across the country. From one end of the spectrum to the other, Darwin's Black Box has established itself as the key intelligent design text -- the one argument that must be addressed in order to determine whether Darwinian evolution is sufficient to explain life as we know it. In a major new Afterword for this edition, Behe explains that the complexity discovered by microbiologists has dramatically increased since the book was first published. That complexity is a continuing challenge to Darwinism, and evolutionists have had no success at explaining it. Darwin's Black Box is more important today than ever.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>Of Pandas and People</title>
	<image>resources_html_m62135712.png</image>
	<location>576.8 DAV</location>
	<link>http://www.christianbook.com/central-question-biological-origins-second-edition/percival-davis/0914513400/pd/513400</link>
	<description>Can your students discern scientific fact from anti-faith fiction? Designed for public school classrooms, this balanced discussion of human origins offers the evidence for intelligent design from biochemistry, genetics, and paleontology without referencing biblical texts. Thoroughly researched and illustrated with helpful diagrams, charts, and color photos, it makes an outstanding supplement to standard high school biology textbooks. Includes an index, glossary, and suggested reading list.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>The Soul of Science</title>
	<image>resources_html_m1214ecf8.png</image>
	<location>560 PEA</location>
	<link>http://www.christianbook.com/soul-science-christian-faith-natural-philosophy/nancy-pearcey/9780891077664/pd/1077669</link>
	<description>Surveys the development of science and it's historic and present relationship to Christianity, and reintroduces believers to their rich intellectual heritage.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>Tho Politically Incorrect Guide to Global Warming</title>
	<image>resources_html_m21f34221.png</image>
	<location> </location>
	<link>http://www.christianbook.com/the-politically-incorrect-guide-global-warming/christopher-horner/9781596985018/pd/985018</link>
	<description>Think Global Warming isn't all environmentalists claim it is? The Politically Incorrect Guide (PIG) to Global Warming will educate you on how environmentalism is really a campaign for more government control over the economy and individual liberty; how 'green' groups are paid for by "congressional schemes"; and why the rationing of energy is a statist design to change your lifestyle against your will. Find what type of alarmism is sweeping the country!</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>True for You But Not for Me</title>
	<image>resources_html_m31bfc293.png</image>
	<location>239 COP</location>
	<link>http://www.christianbook.com/true-you-but-not-for-revised/paul-copan/9780764206504/pd/206500</link>
	<description>Learn to respond to one of the most common objections about Christianity - that it claims to be the only faith. The message of relativism and religious plurality is very popular and its argument is commonly accepted. Here you will find clear explanations to counter those arguments, including: the absolute quality of relativism, the exclusivity of inclusivity, the uniqueness of Jesus, and "What about the unsaved who have never heard?".</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>The Light and The Glory</title>
	<image>resources_html_2f6ddaae.png</image>
	<location>973 MAR</location>
	<link>http://www.christianbook.com/light-glory-revised-expanded-edition-1787/peter-marshall/9780800732714/pd/732714</link>
	<description>Did Columbus believe that God called him west to undiscovered lands? Does American democracy owe its inception to the handful of Pilgrims that settled at Plymouth? If, indeed, there was a specific, divine call upon this nation, is it still valid today? The Light and The Glory answers these questions and many more for history buffs. As readers look at their nation's history from God's point of view, they will begin to have an idea of how much we owe to a very few--and how much is still at stake. Now revised and expanded for the first time in more than thirty years, The Light and The Glory is poised to show new readers just how special their country is.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>Christianity and the Constitution</title>
	<image>resources_html_m515c09.png</image>
	<location>973 ED</location>
	<link>http://www.christianbook.com/christianity-constitution-faith-our-founding-fathers/john-eidsmoe/9780801052316/pd/52319</link>
	<description>Teach your teens the facts about America's Constitution---and introduce them to the Founding Fathers! In this straightforward, readable text, Eidsmoe refutes popular misconceptions about Jefferson's "wall of separation between church and state" and describes the passionately held Christian beliefs that shaped our nation. Includes the full text of the Declaration of Independence and the Constitution.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>The Rewriting of America's History</title>
	<image>resources_html_m60b38bfe.png</image>
	<location>973.6 MIL</location>
	<link>http://www.christianbook.com/christianity-constitution-faith-our-founding-fathers/john-eidsmoe/9780801052316/pd/52319</link>
	<description>Something is happening to original documents, objects d'art, and information about the same concerning our nation's Christian heritage. Priceless, irreplaceable and unique books and other writings from and about the religious inclinations of the pilgrims and founding fathers have gone missing at the Library of Congress. Faith-inspired art illuminating the spiritual basis of America are being removed, obscured or even redefined to exclude their intended faith-based elements. Beyond that, American children are being taught nothing about the Christian foundations of their country while being offered a version of American beginnings based on atheistic, humanistic re-inventions. Catherine Millard is a caretaker of the truths that are actively being suppressed, and in The Rewriting of America's History she finds the provenance of the items and ideas that had once been on display in Washington D.C. and Philadelphia but are now strangely missing. By providing source documentation and other original exhibits from our patriotic forefathers, Millard shows clearly that they intended to build a nation based on the Law of the Lord, not to create a theocracy, but to fashion a haven where any person - Christian, atheist or from any other religion - could enjoy the protection provided for by the original intentions of the founding documents.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>Understanding the Times</title>
	<image>resources_html_27320291.png</image>
	<location>239 NOE</location>
	<link>http://www.summit.org/store/Understanding-the-Times-STUDENT-TEXTBOOK-Christian-School/</link>
	<description>Newly revised and updated with two more worldviews surveyed: Islam and Postmodernism! The abridged hardcover textbook analyzes and compares the six major worldviews impacting our world. This book is a landmark guide to understanding the ideas and forces that are shaping our times. From Christianity to Islam to Humanism to Marxism to the New Age to Postmodernism, Understanding the Times provides Christians with a readable, comprehensive treatment of the most significant religious worldviews operating in Western Civilization.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>Defending Your Faith</title>
	<image>resources_html_m773a65aa.png</image>
	<location> </location>
	<link>http://www.christianbook.com/defending-your-faith-introduction-to-apologetics/r-c-sproul/9781433503153/pd/503153</link>
	<description>In the universities, media, and workplace, Christian beliefs are undermined daily---can you fight for what's right? Outlining the history and fundamentals of apologetics, Sproul explains how reason and scientific inquiry offer strong allies for defending your faith. Great for group study, it equips you for more than just winning arguments, but for changing minds, too! 208 pages, softcover from Crossway.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>I Don't Have Enough Faith to be an Atheist</title>
	<image>resources_html_m466b80b0.png</image>
	<location>239 GEI</location>
	<link>http://www.christianbook.com/dont-have-enough-faith-atheist-ebook/norman-geisler/9781433517037/pd/7272EB</link>
	<description>Norman Geisler and Frank Turek show, first of all, that truth is absolute, exclusive, and knowable. From there, they proceed to demonstrate that the cardinal Christian doctrines are true beyond reasonable doubt, all convincing for you as a Christian to believe, but requiring a leap of negative "faith" if an atheist is to disbelieve them.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>The Young Earth</title>
	<image>resources_html_63ec19de.png</image>
	<location>560 MOR</location>
	<link>http://www.christianbook.com/young-earth-history-present-future-powerpoint/john-morris/9780890514986/pd/514980</link>
	<description>The age of the earth—does it really matter? The answer is vital to understanding not just earth science, but also the biblical record. Dr. John Morris' revised The Young Earth is just the resource you need to examine the scientific, as well as theological, significance of the question of origins.</description>
  </book>
  <book>
    <title>In the Beginning</title>
	<image>resources_html_539db201.png</image>
	<location>560 BRO</location>
	<link>http://www.christianbook.com/beginning-8th-edition-compelling-evidence-creation/walt-brown/9781878026095/pd/026095</link>
	<description>Jumping right to the point, readers will find this book a point-by-point refutation of evolutionist beliefs and affirmation of creationist doctrine. Readers will learn about the author's "hydroplate theory", the social consequences of Darwinism, scriptural answers for what happened during creation, and more. This book is arranged in three parts: The Scientific Case for Creation; Foundations of the Great Deep; and Frequently Asked Questions.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>Reasoning From the Scriptures With the Mormons</title>
	<image>resources_html_m1b69af27.png</image>
	<location>289.3 RHO</location>
	<link>http://www.christianbook.com/reasoning-from-the-scriptures-with-mormons/ron-rhodes/9781565073289/pd/73282</link>
	<description>Their arguments are convincing, their teachings seem indisputable and their stand on what they believe is firm. How can you effectively communicate to the Mormons that their gospel does not match up with the Bible? One of the best ways is to ask penetrating questions. Cult experts Ron Rhodes and Marian Bodine will help you understand the main points of Mormonism and discover where it falls short of God's truth. They then equip you to ask strategic questions that challenge.... The Mormon claim to be the only true church, The reliability of Mormon prophets, The authenticity of the Book of Mormon, Jesus' supposed visit to ancient America, and The Mormon view of God, Jesus, and the Holy Spirit.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>Total Truth</title>
	<image>resources_html_1f95d357.png</image>
	<location>261 PEA</location>
	<link>http://www.christianbook.com/total-truth-liberating-christianity-cultural-captivity/nancy-pearcey/9781433502200/pd/502200</link>
	<description>Does God belong in the public arena of politics, business, law, and education? Or is religion a private and personal matter only? Pearcey challenges 21st-century believers to overcome our cultural double-mindedness and learn to "think Christianly" about secular topics. The included study guide offers practical hands-on steps for crafting an illuminated, faith-based worldview.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>Right from Wrong</title>
	<image>resources_html_2d2b96a1.png</image>
	<location>259.23 MCD</location>
	<link>http://www.christianbook.com/right-from-wrong-josh-mcdowell/9780849936043/pd/36047</link>
	<description>The foundational book for the interdenominational Right from Wrong campaign! Parents, pastors, and youth workers praise this biblical yet contemporary blueprint for passing core Christian values to the next generation. Learn how to teach youth to determine what is absolutely right by helping them understand why certain truths are universal and others are not.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>The New Tolerance</title>
	<image>resources_html_m6462fdae.png</image>
	<location>261 MCD</location>
	<link>http://www.christianbook.com/the-new-tolerance-josh-mcdowell/9780842370882/pd/70886</link>
	<description>How Much "Tolerance" Can We Tolerate?  Best-selling author Josh McDowell and Bob Hostetler unmask the true nature of the cultural movement of "tolerance" in this powerful release. It will not only help you to understand it, but equip you to counter its insidious effects on your faith and your children. In addition, the authors teach you how to: neutralize this threat by discerning truth from error, teach your children to discern between acceptance and approval, and lovingly respond to a hostile culture that seems willing to tolerate just about anything except biblical truth.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>Refuting Evolution</title>
	<image>resources_html_20a6c399.png</image>
	<location> </location>
	<link>http://www.christianbook.com/Christian/Books/product?item_no=0513872</link>
	<description>Dr. Jonathan Sarfati, who expertly defended creation in Refuting Evolution (which has sold over 350,000 copies), goes to bat once again in Refuting Evolution 2. Aimed specifically at the evolutionarily biased PBS television series Evolution, Sarfati adroitly makes light of the inaccuracies and fallacies of evolutionary theory, and offers sound creationist interpretation of the facts. This book also updates creationist arguments such as the plesiosaur reeled in by the Japanese fishing boat, the peppered moths, the men have one less rib than women adage, and much more. Here is a priceless resource for those involved in the ongoing creation/evolution debate.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>Original Intent</title>
	<image>resources_html_m536b3e5e.png</image>
	<location> </location>
	<link>http://www.christianbook.com/original-intent-courts-the-constitution-religion/david-barton/9781932225631/pd/225631</link>
	<description>An essential resource for anyone interested in our nation's religious heritage and the Founders' intended role for the American judicial system. Original Intent combines hundreds of quotes from primary sources with the author's exposition on hot topics such as revisionism, judicial activism, and separation of church and state. A substantial appendix encompasses full texts of the founding documents, biographical sketches of numerous Founders, and extensive reference notes.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>5 Minute Apologist</title>
	<image>resources_html_m1cbff760.png</image>
	<location>239 COR</location>
	<link>http://www.christianbook.com/minute-apologist-maximum-truth-minimum-time/rick-cornish/9781576835050/pd/835057</link>
	<description>Part of being a Christian is telling others about your faith. Sounds easy, but do you know how to answer the tough questions? Are you prepared to respond to skeptical friends and family? With this book, answers to the difficult, honest questions you face are organized topically and marked with tabs for instant access. In daily, five-minute readings, Rick Cornish gives you powerful yet humble words to defend your faith.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>Tactics</title>
	<image>resources_html_m1e916a05.png</image>
	<location> </location>
	<link>http://www.christianbook.com/tactics-plan-discussing-your-christian-convictions/gregory-koukl/9780310282921/pd/282921</link>
	<description>Discuss your Christian convictions to others with grace and confidence. Learn to gracefully negotiate those awkward moments when others challenge you with oft-repeated arguments against the Christian beliefs. Professor Greg Koukl has successfully defended the Christian faith under fire and he wants to show you how a few relatively easy tactics can help you as well.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>Do Fish Know They're Wet?</title>
	<image>resources_html_m50cf8878.png</image>
	<location>239 NEV</location>
	<link>http://www.amazon.com/Fish-Know-Theyre-Wet-World-Without/dp/0801065186/ref=sr_1_1</link>
	<description>Do Fish Know They're Wet? Challenges students and young adults to compare a Christian worldview with other competing opinions of our culture. Inside you'll learn: how and why various philosophies and subtle distortions of the truth affect arguments and lifestyle choices, what it really means to have a Christian worldview, and how to apply your worldview in everything you see and do.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>The Death of Truth</title>
	<image>resources_html_137bf66c.png</image>
	<location>261 MCC</location>
	<link>http://www.christianbook.com/the-death-of-truth/dennis-mccallum/9781556617249/pd/17240</link>
	<description>Postmodernism can be broken down into three beliefs - humans are just cogs in a social machine (not individuals created in the image of God), are not autonomous (simply products of their culture), and are never objective or rational (as 'reason' is perceived as relational). While for some this remains just the latest direction philosophy is directing culture, the spiritually astute recognize it as the latest coordinated effort in undermining biblical Christianity. This new belief system confronts scriptural truth on many fronts: by denying the validity of the Bible, denigrating the human condition and redefining Christian truths to fit the mold of a multi-cultural ecumenical spiritual message.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>Economics in One Lesson</title>
	<image>resources_html_m701805a6.png</image>
	<location> </location>
	<link>http://www.summit.org/store/Economics-In-One-Lesson/</link>
	<description>"[Economics In One Lesson] is a brilliant performance. It says precisely the things which need most saying and says them with rare courage and integrity. I know of no other modern book from which the intelligent layman can learn so much about the basic truths of economics in so short a time." F.A Hayek, 1974, Nobel Laureate in Economic Science, Crown Trade Paperbacks, NY.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>Facts, Not Fear</title>
	<image>resources_html_25ecfcf5.png</image>
	<location>560 SAN</location>
	<link>http://www.amazon.com/Facts-Not-Fear-Teaching-Environment/dp/0889751943/ref=sr_1_1</link>
	<description>Facts, Not Fear is a guidebook countering the irresponsible claims of environmental extremists, giving a more balanced view of the many environmental issues encountered today. In simple, non-technical language, authors Michael Sanera and Jane Shaw explain the myths and facts concerning many major environmental topics, and show you how to set the record straight. Each of the 20 topical chapters was reviewed by acknowledged experts, and include answers to questions about the environment commonly asked by children and suggestions for easy-to-do activities.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>The New Absolutes</title>
	<image>resources_html_495cfeb9.png</image>
	<location>239 WAT</location>
	<link>http://www.amazon.com/New-Absolutes-William-D-Watkins/dp/0764220195/ref=sr_1_1</link>
	<description>Those who claim tolerance and decry moral absolutes are the very ones imposing on society - Our society's problems are no longer "out there" somewhere. They affect our everyday work and family life and how we raise our children. Under the guise of tolerance, relativism, and a professed attitude of "live and let live," new ideas are being advanced of what is true and right for all of us: Family is any grouping of two or more people, Religion should be banned from public life, Any sexual activity between consenting parties is moral, Politically incorrect viewpoints should be silenced. Our culture's consensus of what is true and right is shifting not because we as a society have become tolerant of all views and lifestyles, but because we are trading what we once believed to be true for new beliefs. Ten beliefs once held to be absolutely true are being trampled by ten new beliefs; the personally and socially destructive new absolutes. If the new absolutes are not exposed and opposed they will lead to cultural collapse.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>The Evolution of a Creationist</title>
	<image>resources_html_5dc4436c.png</image>
	<location>560 MAR</location>
	<link>http://www.christianbook.com/the-evolution-of-a-creationist-series/pd/975577</link>
	<description>A companion book to the video series "Incredible Creatures That Defy Evolution", Dr. Jobe Martin chronicles his personal journey from traditional scientist to creationist. The book takes a look at animals that break all of the evolutionary "rules." It examines the many problems with evolutionary theory and shows why the Bible is an excellent book of science. Easy to read, this 200 page book is a must for Christian students, Sunday School classes and anyone who is interested in solving the conflict between evolution and the Bible. The goal of The Evolution of a Creationist is to provide the reader with easily accessible information on the creation versus evolution controversy. The book is a condensation and simplification of more than 20 years of studies that moved Dr. Jobe Martin from unquestioning belief in Darwinian evolution to undoubting trust in the six-day creation by God, as presented in the Biblical account.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>Politically Correct Death</title>
	<image>resources_html_387eb5b2.png</image>
	<location> </location>
	<link>http://www.amazon.com/Politically-Correct-Death-Answering-Arguments/dp/0801010500</link>
	<description>Thorough explanation of sixty-nine ethical and philosophical arguments sometimes given to defend a pro-choice position and persuasive pro life responses to each.  The most comprehensive book on the subject, Beckwith takes each argument in favor of abortion and systematically destroys it.  If you are engaged in debates on the subject, you will want this book.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>Pro Life Answers to Pro Choice Questions</title>
	<image>resources_html_5411e635.png</image>
	<location> </location>
	<link>http://www.amazon.com/Pro-Life-Answers-Pro-Choice-Arguments-Expanded/dp/1576737519</link>
	<description>Written by one of the most committed, yet compassionate pro-life activists, this book will guarantee that you are never at a loss for words in the abortion battle.  Alcorn methodically dissects pro-choice arguments, showing you how to persuasively refute them.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>America's Christian History</title>
	<image>resources_html_7e90ab64.png</image>
	<location> </location>
	<link>http://www.amazon.com/Americas-Christian-History-Gary-DeMar/dp/0915815168</link>
	<description>This is an excellent, factual book about how biblical principles and Christian values guided the founding fathers in establishing America.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>Can Man Live Without God</title>
	<image>resources_html_17fbd6c.png</image>
	<location> </location>
	<link>http://www.amazon.com/Can-Man-Live-without-God/dp/0849939437</link>
	<description>This book explains why atheism, so small in number of believers but so large in influence, is emotionally and intellectually unsatisfying.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>Is Jesus the Only Savior?</title>
	<image>resources_html_44396b73.png</image>
	<location> </location>
	<link>http://www.amazon.com/Jesus-Only-Savior-Ronald-Nash/dp/0310443911</link>
	<description>Jesus said, "no one comes to the Father but through me." Was he telling the truth? Many modern day scholars say no, but Ron Nash says yes and explains in articulate, powerful arguments.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>Mere Christianity</title>
	<image>resources_html_m49c699ad.png</image>
	<location> </location>
	<link>http://www.amazon.com/Mere-Christianity-C-S-Lewis/dp/0060652926</link>
	<description>This classic book by the common man's philosopher provides an especially cogent presentation of the moral "proof" for God and helps Christians understand the radical nature of their faith.  Only Christianity, as Lewis explains, can completely account for the existence of moral absolutes and conscience.  This is a great book to give to non-Christian friends who like to think.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>Why I am a Christian</title>
	<image>resources_html_m2eacff47.png</image>
	<location> </location>
	<link>http://www.amazon.com/Why-Am-Christian-Leading-Thinkers/dp/080106712X</link>
	<description>How can anyone claim to have the truth? Can anyone really prove the existence of God? Isn't it naive to believe in miracles? Doesn't evolution prove that the Bible's creation story is false? If God is so powerful and good, why is there so much suffering in the world? These are crucial questions that many Christians wrestle with. They are also the type of questions asked by skeptics of the faith. Why I Am a Christian offers compelling answers that will free Christians from doubt and clear away obstacles to faith for unbelievers. Beginning with the topics of moral relativism and knowable truth, the book progresses to questions about belief in God, the reliability of the Bible, and the identity of Jesus as the Messiah, the Son of God. It concludes with three chapters on what it means to make a commitment to follow Christ. The contributors to this revised edition are expert witnesses for the Christian faith. They include an astronomer, a mechanical engineer, a trial lawyer, a religious historian, a philosopher, a Jewish Christian, a former atheist, a former skeptic, and a former Muslim.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>Art and the Bible</title>
	<image>resources_html_763f01c1.png</image>
	<location> </location>
	<link>http://www.amazon.com/Art-Bible-Classics-Francis-Schaeffer/dp/083083401X</link>
	<description>About the Book "The lordship of Christ should include an interest in the arts," writes Francis Schaeffer. "A Christian should use these arts to the glory of God, not just as tracts, mind you, but as things of beauty to the praise of God." Many Christians, wary of creating graven images, have steered clear of artistic creativity. But the Bible offers a robust affirmation of the arts. The human impulse to create reflects our being created in the image of a creator God. Art and the Bible has been a foundational work for generations of Christians in the arts. In this book's classic essays, Francis Schaeffer first examines the scriptural record of the use of various art forms, and then establishes a Christian perspective on art. With clarity and vigor, Schaeffer explains why "the Christian is the one whose imagination should fly beyond the stars."</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>Modern Art and the Death of a Culture</title>
	<image>resources_html_3145e842.png</image>
	<location> </location>
	<link>http://www.amazon.com/Modern-Art-Death-Culture-Rookmaaker/dp/0891077995</link>
	<description>This Christian classic gives a strong biblical worldview perspective of the arts--not just a knee-jerk reactionary perspective.  Anyone interested in or majoring in music, visual arts or theater needs to read this book.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>Cutting-Edge Bioethics</title>
	<image>resources_html_m25e9717e.png</image>
	<location> </location>
	<link>http://www.amazon.com/Cutting-Edge-Bioethics-Christian-Exploration-Technologies/dp/0802849598</link>
	<description>This book from the Center for Bioethics and Human Dignity provides a faith-based evaluation of recent technologies and trends in bioethics--including the current debate surrounding stem cell research. Fifteen noted scholars and medical practitioners discuss some of today's new and controversial work in biomedicine--xenotransplantation, artificial intelligence, cybernetics, and more--and evaluate from a Christian perspective both the science and the ethical questions it raises. Designed to orient general readers to the current state of biomedical research, Cutting-Edge Bioethics is must reading for anyone wishing to confront and wrestle with the challenging moral issues posed by this ever-advancing field.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>All God's Children and Blue Suede Shoes</title>
	<image>resources_html_m38e9298a.png</image>
	<location> </location>
	<link>http://www.amazon.com/Gods-Children-Blue-Suede-Shoes/dp/0891075380</link>
	<description>Skillfully analyzes American popular culture, tracing its development and describing its influence. Part of the Turning Point Christian Worldview Series.</description>
  </book>
  
  <book>
    <title>Connecting</title>
	<image>resources_html_71b41a4.png</image>
	<location> </location>
	<link>http://www.amazon.com/Connecting-Mentoring-Relationships-Need-Succeed/dp/0891096388</link>
	<description>CONNECTING by Paul D. Stanley and J. Robert Clinton, explains how we were meant for each other. None of us are fully equipped to excel in life. Our weaknesses, blind spots, limited capabilities and lack of experience all point to one thing-interdependence. Which is why connecting with others plays such an indispensable role in healthy development. Having access to the wisdom, experience, vision, and direction of those who have gone before can put you years ahead of where you'd be on your own. So why don't we place more of a priority on developing these essential, empowering relationships? Stanley and Clinton say the main reason we miss out is that we simply don't understand the true nature of mentoring-a problem that is easily overcome.</description>
  </book>
</resources>